xwireless.net 2018-05-14

# Privacy Policy - Enterprise Class Bulk SMS Gateway

#### Privacy Policy

Your Personal Information

Client information collected by Explorer Technologies is for accounts, records and billing purposes. We reserve the right to use your information to monitor usage of products and services, and to contact you using it when we deem it necessary. We may send new members welcome information (depending on the service, sometimes giving account information, general information, or payment details). Established members will periodically receive information deemed necessary by Explorer Technologies. These communications do not infringe the users privacy and are part of the Explorer Technologies service. Your information is kept private and secure and is not disclosed to third parties other than to perform actions on behalf of Explorer Technologies.

Your data uploads

All contact data (including merge field data contained in uploaded database fields) is stored privately and securely by Explorer Technologies and is in no way disclosed to any third party. Data is used for no other purpose than to send the item you requested to the number you supplied and for logging and security as outlined within the privacy policy.

Online Privacy

Cookies will be used on the site for storing details such as login information when you are connected to your account. Cookies are here to increase your security, not infringe on your privacy. Logins will be processed through a secure connection.

Logging

Access to this website and all actions performed within your account are logged. These logs, however, are only made available to law enforcement agencies and employees for which access to such details is essential. SMS messages transmitted through this system are also logged for legal reasons.

Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. We will make every effort to help the Police services with their enquiries if we believe it is in our users' interests and to protect the Explorer Technologies service.
